m1finance.com 2019-06-13

# M1 Finance | Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy ("Policy") covers the following affiliated companies in the M1 family of companies: M1 Holdings Inc., M1 Finance LLC, M1 Advisory Services LLC, and M1 Spend LLC. These entities are collectively referred to as "M1," "affiliated companies," "we," "us," and "our" throughout this Policy.

 **Overview**

We are committed to maintaining the privacy and confidentiality of our customers' personal information. In the course of offering and providing financial products and services, we collect and maintain certain personal information about you. This information can come from information you provide on applications or other forms, through your inquiries by mail, e-mail or telephone, or by other means.

This Policy explains what personal information we collect and how we use and share such personal information. It also explains what you can do to limit the use and sharing of your personal information. We do not disclose personal information about our customers to non-affiliated third parties, except as described below.

 **Updates to this Policy**

As required by federal law, we will notify you of our privacy policy annually. We reserve the right to modify this policy at any time, and if we do change it, you will be informed promptly.

 **Online Privacy**

M1 Finance may periodically collect information from you through automated means. When you browse our site, use the iOS and Android applications, use our services, or read our emails or newsletters, we may use "cookies" or other online tracking mechanisms (including pixel tags, web beacons, clear GIFs and device fingerprints) in order to provide better service, facilitate your use of the site or services, store online preferences, track usage of the site or services, tailor the marketing of business services, or enhance security.

Some of our cookies are used for web analytics and intelligence about our site. We may also use web beacons or other technologies for similar purposes and we may include these in marketing email messages or our newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and links clicked on. Web beacons do not place information on your device, but may work in conjunction with cookies to monitor online activity.

By using our site or applications you agree that we can place cookies on your device and use other online tracking mechanisms as explained in this privacy notice. You may be able to control your acceptance of cookies and similar technologies on a website, and most devices and browsers offer their own privacy settings for cookies. You will need to manage your cookie settings for each device and browser you use. If you do not accept cookies, you may experience some inconvenience in your use of some sites and online products. For example, a website may not be able to recognize your device and you may need to answer challenge questions or provide additional information each time you log on.

 **Interest-based advertising**

We use "interest-based" ads, which are also known as "online behavioral advertising." We may partner with ad networks and other advertising providers (“Advertising Providers”) who serve ads on behalf of us and others on non-affiliated sites. Some of these third parties may use cookies and other technologies to collect information about your online activities over time and across third party websites or online services to deliver advertising based on your interests and preferences, as inferred from your browsing history. Some of these ads may be personalized, meaning that they are intended to be relevant to you based on information that M1 and its Advertising Providers collect about your visits to this site and elsewhere over time.

 **Protecting information**

With regard to our internal security procedures, we restrict access to your personal and account information to those employees who "need to know" the information in order to provide products and services to you. We maintain reasonable physical, administrative, and technical safeguards to protect your personal information. We conduct regular internal audits of our business practices and procedures in order to protect your personal information.

 **Plaid**

We use Plaid Inc. (“Plaid”) to gather End User’s data from financial institutions. By using our service, you grant us and Plaid the right, power, and authority to act on your behalf to access and transmit your personal and financial information from the relevant financial institution. You agree to your personal and financial information being transferred, stored, and processed by Plaid in accordance with the [Plaid Privacy Policy](https://plaid.com/legal/).

For questions about our policy, or for additional copies of this notice, please call us at [888.714.6674](tel:888.714.6674).
